[
    {
        "topic": "SYSTEM ARCHITECTURE",
        "subtopics": [
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "aaa",
                "b": "bbb",
                "c": "ccc",
                "d": "ddd",
                "correct": "b"
            },
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "aaa",
                "b": "bbb",
                "c": "ccc",
                "d": "ddd",
                "correct": "c"
            },
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "aaa",
                "b": "bbb",
                "c": "ccc",
                "d": "ddd",
                "correct": "c"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "topic": "LINUX INSTALLATION AND PACKAGE MANAGEMENT",
        "subtopics": [
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "aaa",
                "b": "bbb",
                "c": "ccc",
                "d": "ddd",
                "correct": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "To store data in a structured format.",
                "b": "To analyze data using statistical methods.",
                "c": "To represent data graphically to identify patterns and insights.",
                "d": "To clean and preprocess data.",
                "correct": "c"
            },
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "aaa",
                "b": "bbb",
                "c": "ccc",
                "d": "ddd",
                "correct": "b"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "topic": "GNU AND UNIX COMMANDS",
        "subtopics": [
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "aaa",
                "b": "bbb",
                "c": "ccc",
                "d": "ddd",
                "correct": "b"
            },
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "aaa",
                "b": "bbb",
                "c": "ccc",
                "d": "ddd",
                "correct": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "aaa",
                "b": "bbb",
                "c": "ccc",
                "d": "ddd",
                "correct": "b"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "topic": "DEVICES, LINUX FILESYSTEMS, FILESYSTEM HIERARCHY STANDARD",
        "subtopics": [
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "aaa",
                "b": "bbb",
                "c": "ccc",
                "d": "ddd",
                "correct": "b"
            },
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "aaa",
                "b": "bbb",
                "c": "ccc",
                "d": "ddd",
                "correct": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "a": "aaa",
                "b": "bbb",
                "c": "ccc",
                "d": "ddd",
                "correct": "b"
            }
        ]
    }
]
